<resources>


    <string name="appname">Lymphatic Filariasis (LF), commonly known as <b>elephantiasis</b> is a disfiguring and disabling disease, usually acquired in childhood. In the early stages, there are either no symptoms or non-specific symptoms. Although there are no outward symptoms, the lymphatic system is damaged. This stage can last for several years. Infected persons sustain the transmission of the disease. The long term physical consequences are painful swollen limbs (lymphoedema or elephantiasis). Hydrocele in males is also common in endemic areas.\n\nDue to damaged lymphatic system, patients with lymphoedema have frequent attacks of infection causing high fever and severe pain. Patients may be bed-ridden for several days and normal routine activities become difficult. Such attacks not only cause acute physical suffering but also directly impede the earning capacity of the individual. Lymphatic filariasis is estimated to be one of the leading causes of disability worldwide. Elimination of the disease is an important tool for poverty alleviation and economic development.\n\n\n <b><h1><centre>Symptoms</centre> </h1></b>\n \n1. <b>Asymptomatic Phase</b>: In many cases, especially during the early stages of infection, individuals may not exhibit any noticeable symptoms.\n\n2. <b>Acute Phase</b>: During this phase, which can occur weeks to months after infection, symptoms may include:

Fever
Chills
Skin rashes
Swelling of the lymph nodes (lymphadenitis)
Pain and inflammation in the affected limbs (lymphangitis)
Headache
Muscle pain
Fatigue
Nausea \n\n<b>3. Chronic Phase</b>: If left untreated, filariasis can progress to the chronic phase, characterized by the following symptoms:

Lymphedema: Swelling, usually in the limbs, due to blockage or damage to the lymphatic vessels.
Elephantiasis: Severe and disfiguring swelling of the limbs, genitalia, breasts, or other body parts. This condition is often irreversible.
Hydrocele: Swelling of the scrotum in males due to the accumulation of fluid.
Recurrent fevers and inflammation in affected areas.
Skin thickening and discoloration.\n\n <b>4. Secondary Infections</b>: Individuals with lymphedema or elephantiasis are more prone to bacterial skin infections, such as cellulitis, which can exacerbate symptoms and lead to complications.</string>
    <string name="lf_content_kannada">ಲಿಂಫಾಟಿಕ್ ಫಿಲಾರಿಯಾಸಿಸ್ (ಎಲ್ಎಫ್), ಸಾಮಾನ್ಯವಾಗಿ ಗಂಡುಮಕ್ಕಳಲ್ಲಿ ಪಡೆಯಲ್ಪಟ್ಟಿದ್ದು, ಗರ್ಭಾವಸ್ಥೆಯಲ್ಲಿಯೇ ತಗುಲಿಕೊಂಡಿದ್ದು, ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಗೆ ಸಾಧನೆ ಆಗದಿರುವ ಒಂದು ಬಿಕ್ಕಟ್ಟು ಮತ್ತು ಮಾನಸಿಕ ಅಸ್ವಸ್ಥತೆಯ ರೋಗ, ವಾಸ್ತವವಾಗಿಯೂ ಮಕ್ಕಳಲ್ಲಿ ಸಾಧಾರಣವಾಗಿ ಪಡೆಯಲ್ಪಟ್ಟಿದ್ದು. ಆರಂಭದ ಹಂತಗಳಲ್ಲಿ, ಯಾವುದೇ ಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳಿಲ್ಲ ಅಥವಾ ಪ್ರತ್ಯಕ್ಷ ಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳಿರಬಹುದು. ಹೊರಗಿನ ಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳಿಲ್ಲದೆ ಇದ್ದರೂ, ಲಿಂಫಾಟಿಕ್ ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆ ಹಾನಿಯಾಗಿದೆ. ಈ ಹಂತ ಅನೇಕ ವರ್ಷಗಳವರೆಗೆ ಇರಬಹುದು. ಸಂಕ್ರಮಿತ ವ್ಯಕ್ತಿಗಳು ರೋಗದ ಹರಡುವನ್ನು ಹೊಂದಿದ್ದಾರೆ. ದೀರ್ಘ ಕಾಲದ ಶಾರೀರಿಕ ಪರಿಣಾಮಗಳು ಬೇಕಾದಾಗ, ನೋವಾಯಿತು ಸೆಳೆದ ಅಂಗಗಳು (ಲಿಂಫೋಡಿಮಾ ಅಥವಾ ಎಲೆಫೆಂಟಿಯಾಸಿಸ್). ಆದಮೇಲೆ, ಉದ್ದೇಶಿತ ಪ್ರದೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಗಂಡುಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಹೈಡ್ರೊಸೆಲ್ ಸಾಮಾನ್ಯವಾಗಿದೆ.

        ಹಾಗೆ ಹಾನಿಯಾದ ಲಿಂಫಾಟಿಕ್ ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆಯಿಂದ, ಲಿಂಫೋಡಿಮಾ ಹೊಂದಿರುವ ರೋಗಿಗಳು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಪ್ರಬಲ ಜ್ವರ ಮತ್ತು ತೀವ್ರ ನೋವಿನ ದಾಳಿಗಳನ್ನು ಹೊಂದುತ್ತಾರೆ. ರೋಗಿಗಳು ಹಲವು ದಿನಗಳ .\n\n\n <b><centre><h1>ರೋಗಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳು</h1></centre></b>\n\n <b>1.ಅಲ್ಪಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳು</b>: ಅನೇಕ ಸಂದರ್ಭಗಳಲ್ಲಿ, ವಿಶೇಷವಾಗಿ ಸಂಕ್ರಮಣದ ಹೊರತುಪಡಿಸಿದರೆ, ವ್ಯಕ್ತಿಗಳು ಯಾವುದೇ ಗುರುತುಗಳನ್ನು ಹೊಂದದೆ ಇರಬಹುದು.\n\n <b>ತೀವ್ರ ಚರಣ:</b>ಸಂಕ್ರಮಣದ ನಂತರ ಕೆಲವು ವಾರಗಳಿಂದ ಅಥವಾ ತಿಂಗಳುಗಳಿಂದ ನಡೆಯುವ ಈ ಚರಣದಲ್ಲಿ, ಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳು ಈ ರೀತಿ ಇರಬಹುದು:

ಜ್ವರ
ಚಳಿ
ಚರ್ಮದ ಚರ್ಮಿಗಳು
ಲಿಂಗಗಳ ವಿಪರೀತ ಬೆನ್ನುಹತ್ತಿದರು
ಪ್ರಭುತ್ವದ ಬಲವಾಗಿರುವ ಮೀಸೆ
ತಲೆಗಟ್ಟಲು
ಸಾಯಂತ್ರ ನೋವು
ಮಾಂಸಪೇಶಿ ನೋವು
ಜಾರತನ\n\n<b>ಚಿರಚರಣ:</b>ಕುಲುಮೆಯಾದ ಅವಸ್ಥೆಯನ್ನು ಬಿಟ್ಟರೆ, ಸಂಕ್ರಮಣವನ್ನು ನಿಯಂತ್ರಿಸಲು ಬಿಟ್ಟರೆ, ಮುಂದುವರಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ:

ನಾಡಿಗಳ ಗುಲ್ಮೋದ್ರೇಕ
ಎಲೆಫ್ಯಾಂಟಿಯಾಸಿಸ್: ಅತ್ಯಂತ ತೀವ್ರ ಹಾಗೂ ಮುಂಗೋಪಾಯ ಗುಲ್ಮೋದ್ರೇಕ
ಹೈಡ್ರೋಸೀಲ್: ಜಲಮಯವಾಗಿ ಗುಲ್ಮೋದ್ರೇಕ
ಪ್ರತಿಧ್ವನಿಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಮುಂಗೋಪಾಯ ಪ್ರಭುತ್ವಗಳು
ಚರ್ಮ ದಪ್ಪತ್ತು ಮತ್ತು ಬಣ್ಣದ ಬದಲಾವಣೆ\n\n <b>ಶ್ರೇಣಿ ಸಂಕ್ರಾಮಗಳು:</b>ಲಿಂಗಮಾಂಸಪೇಶಿ ಅಥವಾ ಎಲೆಫ್ಯಾಂಟಿಯಾಸಿಸ್‌ನ ಉಳಿತಾಯಗಳಿಗೆ ಪ್ರವಾಹವನ್ನು ನೀಡಿದವರು ಬೆರಳಿನಲ್ಲಿ ಕಿರಿಕುಳದ ಹೊಲವನ್ನು ಕೊನೆಗಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಬಹುದು, ಈ ಲಕ್ಷಣಗಳನ್ನು ಗತಿಸಿ ಸಂಕ್ರಾಮಕವಾಗಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ಕಠಿಣತೆಗಳಿಗೆ ಒಳಗಾಗಬಹುದು.</string>


    <string name="app_name">Health Care App</string>
    <string name="main_activity_description">Discute avec tes mentors, tout simplement.</string>

    <string name="login">Connexion</string>
    <string name="chat_with_mentor">Discute avec un mentor</string>

    <!-- NOTIFICATION SERVICE -->
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="notification_title">"Vous avez reçu une notification"</string>

    <!-- MAIN ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="error_not_connected">Vous devez vous connecter !</string>
    <string name="error_authentication_canceled">Authentification annulée&#8230;</string>
    <string name="error_no_internet">Aucune connexion internet !</string>
    <string name="error_unknown_error">Une erreur inconnue s\'est produite&#8230;</string>
    <string name="connection_succeed">Authentification réussie !</string>
    <string name="button_login_text_logged">Afficher le profil</string>
    <string name="button_login_text_not_logged">Connexion</string>

    <!-- LOGIN ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="toolbar_title_login_activity">Votre Profil</string>
    <string name="text_input_username">Nom d\'utilisateur</string>
    <string name="text_view_email">Adresse email :</string>
    <string name="button_update_account">Mettre à jour le nom d\'utilisateur</string>
    <string name="button_delete_account">Supprimer mon compte</string>
    <string name="button_sign_out_account">Déconnexion</string>
    <string name="info_no_email_found">Auncune adresse email</string>
    <string name="info_no_username_found">Aucun nom d\'utilisateur</string>
    <string name="popup_message_confirmation_delete_account">Es-tu sûr(e) de vouloir supprimer ton compte ?</string>
    <string name="popup_message_choice_yes">Oui !</string>
    <string name="popup_message_choice_no">Non</string>
    <string name="check_box_is_mentor">Etes-vous un mentor ?</string>

    <!-- MENTOR_CHAT ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="toolbar_title_mentor_chat_activity">Chats de discussions</string>
    <string name="text_input_title_mentor_chat_activity">Composer votre message</string>
    <string name="button_title_mentor_chat_activity">ENVOYER</string>
    <string name="text_view_mentor_chat_error">Ce fil de discussion ne contient pour le moment aucun message&#8230;</string>
    <string name="popup_title_permission_files_access">Cette application a besoin de permission pour fonctionner.</string>
    <string name="toast_title_no_image_chosen">Aucune image choisie&#8230;</string>
    <!-- Book api -->
    <string name="thumbnail">thumbnail</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="price">40 $</string>
    <string name="author">Author</string>


    <string name="search">SEARCH</string>
    <string name="hint">Enter your query </string>
    <string name="description_image_view">Template for  the image</string>
    <string name="description_divider">Divider</string>
    <string name="Failed_to_Load_data">Please check your Internet Connection</string>
    <string name="NO_RESULT">No matching results</string>

    <string-array name="fiche_type">
        <item>Consultation</item>
        <item>Hospitalisation</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="specialite_spinner">
        <item>General Physician</item>
        <item>Expert Filariasis Doctor</item>
        <item>Nurse</item>
        <item>Staff</item>
        <item>Junior Doctor</item>
        <item>Intern</item>
        <item>Medicine Incharge</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="blood_spinner">
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
        <item>AB-</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>O-</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!--<string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
        -->
</resources>

